and okay Now about asking people for money,
y vale Ya de pedir dinerito a la gente
get to work and now I'm on a
poneros a trabajar y ahora estoy en un
show that's from Netflix but I have to
programa que es de Netflix pero tengo
say that I'm from the
que decir que yo soy de la fábrica de la
TV factory to several agencies that stop it, they
tele a varias agencias que la paran le
say the same thing about asking for money on
dice lo mismo esto de pidiendo dinero en
YouTube that I don't know what Because I've
YouTube que no sé qué Porque yo he
heard another different click that says
escuchado otro clic diferente que dice
Yes now the journalists have gone to
Sí ahora los periodistas se han ido a
YouTube I'm going to ask for money what I want to
YouTube voy a pedir dinero lo que quiero
say I simply one thing keep
decir yo simplemente una cosa seguí
asking for money or rather it says ask for
pidiendo dinerito o sea dice pide
money because here is the service Because
dinerito porque aquí servicio Porque
here are the Super chat because here are
aquí los Super chat porque aquí están
the members Belén have you realized
los miembros Belén tú te has dado cuenta
queen that in the same in the same in the
reina que en el mismo en el mismo en el
same Clean that we've seen from you you're
mismo Clean que hemos visto tuyo estás
messing with the youtubers because
metiéndote con los youtubers porque la
people pay the membership And you're
gente le paga la membresía Y estás
promoting the Netflix series for
promocionando la serie de Netflix para
next month You know that on Netflix you
el mes que viene Tú sabes que Netflix
have to pay the membership and Netflix
hay que pagar la membresía y Netflix
lives off the membership what is
vive de la membresía lo que es la
ignorance and what is wanting to give a
ignorancia y lo que es el querer dar un
zasca and wanting to give you the
zasca y el querer darte la de